accounting-simplified.com 2012-05-02

# Accounting-Simplified: Free Financial Accounting study resources

At www.accounting-simplified.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.accounting-simplified.com and how it is used.

## Log Files

Like many other Web sites, www.accounting-simplified.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

www.accounting-simplified.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

## DoubleClick DART Cookie

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.accounting-simplified.com
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.accounting-simplified.com and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) or by visiting Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.accounting-simplified.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.accounting-simplified.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.accounting-simplified.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

## Google Analytics

Google Analytics is a web analytics tool that helps website owners understand how visitors interact with their website. Google Analytics customers can view a variety of reports about how visitors engage with their website so they can improve it. Google Analytics collects information anonymously. It reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. Google Analytics uses first-party [cookies](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy_faq.html) which are used to store information, such as what time the current visit occurred, whether the visitor has been to the site before, and what site referred the visitor to the web page. Browsers do not share first-party cookies across domains.

Google Analytics collects the IP address of website visitors in order to provide website owners a sense of where in the world their visitors come from. Google Analytics does not report the actual IP address information to Google Analytics customers. However, personal information of a visitor (such as e-mail address) is not collected by Google Analytics.

www.accounting-simplified.com uses Google Analytics to track visitor interactions. If you do not wish to share data about your site visit you may disable cookies through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
